{
    "id": "edd1228b7baf4dfcab7f5959e051829f",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The two brothers quarreled with ……………………..",
            "description": "Each other refers to two people one another refers to more than two people.",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2b57bb449dd641b6926f473f5112f563"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must love ………………………….",
            "description": "Each other refers to two people one another refers to more than two people. Each other is also possible here in a less careful style.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5745dcf358e545168f3bbe2f98ab09cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let ………………………….. buy something to eat.",
            "description": "Let is a verb. A pronoun used as the object of a verb should be in its object form.",
            "answers": [
                "we",
                "us"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b7bf5c4cc604ddd8a046b4add9b8c5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not as tall as …………………………..",
            "description": "Object pronouns are common after as and than.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "91a23136f84e4701b2a4dd70242de449"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of the boys ………………………………. given a present.",
            "description": "We use a singular verb after each.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc7434c373f8420e91162bb3c18d056a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is older than …………………...",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "I am",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "01d7879d5e194f4790e25eb81e899369"
        },
        {
            "question": "People starve when …………………………… have no money.",
            "description": "Use they to refer to the plural noun people.",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "he",
                "they"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e4ab0ec18e734890ad8a3ad355762f6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like …………………………… kind of movies.",
            "description": "Use this with kind and these with kinds.",
            "answers": [
                "this",
                "these"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cd02d3731b494c70bab5065e4faa4f2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not like these ………………………….. of people.",
            "description": "Use sorts with these and those. ",
            "answers": [
                "sort",
                "sorts"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b9e9eee114254d68a83b02ba6e1ccd18"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. a cloudy day, we did not go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Being",
                "It being"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "174aaa256c4047a5aa8c12d38594bfc3"
        },
        {
            "question": "My handwriting is better than .............................",
            "description": "Your handwriting cannot be better than your friend it can only be better than the handwriting (=that) of your friend. ",
            "answers": [
                "my friend",
                "that of my friend",
                "those of my friend"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b8836efcb9e4eee8d4a451683386b38"
        },
        {
            "question": "My house is smaller ...................................",
            "description": "Theirs means their house.",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5aba8b55b7b400da909123e83a181ab"
        }
    ]
}